<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>
    <string name="dummy_location">Dummy Location</string>
    <string name="baguio_city">Baguio City, Philippines</string>
    <string name="boracay">Boracay Island, Philippines</string>
    <string name="cebu_city">Cebu City</string>
    <string name="palawan">Palawan, Philippines</string>
    <string name="dummy_title">Article Title</string>

    <string name="baguio_panagbenga_title">Panagbenga Festival</string>
    <string name="baguio_panagbenga_desc">Panagbenga Festival (English: Flower Festival) is a month-long annual flower festival occurring in Baguio. The term is of Malayo-Polynesian origin, meaning \"season of blooming\". The festival, held during the month of February, was created as a tribute to the city\'s flowers and as a way to rise up from the devastation of the 1990 Luzon earthquake. The festival includes floats that are covered mostly with flowers not unlike those used in Pasadena\'s Rose Parade. The festival also includes street dancing, presented by dancers clad in flower-inspired costumes, that is inspired by the Bendian, an Ibaloi dance of celebration that came from the Cordillera region.\n\nAside from boosting the economy through tourism, the festival also helped the younger generation of indigenous people to rediscover their culture\'s old traditions. The indigenous people were first wary with government-led tourism because of the threat that they will interfere or change their communities\' rituals.</string>
    <string name="baguio_the_mansion_title">The Mansion</string>
    <string name="baguio_the_mansion_desc">The Mansion House (also known as the The Mansion) is the official summer residence of the President of the Philippines. The mansion is located in the summer capital of the country, Baguio, situated around 5,000 feet (1,500 m) asl in the Cordillera Central Range of northern Luzon.\n\nThe Mansion House was built in 1908 to serve as the official summer residence of U.S. Governor-Generals at the instance of Governor-General William Cameron Forbes. The name is derived from the summer cottage in New England of Governor Forbes whose administration the original Mansion House was built under. Architect William E. Parsons, based on preliminary plans by architect Daniel H. Burnham, the planner of the city of Baguio, designed the mountain retreat following the tenets of the City Beautiful Movement. In 1910, the meeting of the Second Philippine Legislature was held at the Mansion House for three weeks.\n\nWith the inauguration of the Philippine Commonwealth, the Mansion along with Malacañan Palace was turned over to the Philippine president. The High Commissioner to the Philippines, the successor to the Governor-General as the highest American official in the Philippines and representative of the United States Government, then built The American Residence, completed in 1940.</string>
    <string name="baguio_burnham_park_title">Burnham Park</string>
    <string name="baguio_burnham_park_desc">Burnham Park is a 32.84 hectare urban park located at the heart of the Baguio, in the Philippines. It was named after the American architect and urban planner, Daniel Hudson Burnham who laid the plans for the city. Several stretch of roads around the park lead to Camp John Hay, a former recreational base of the United States Armed Forces in the Philippines.\n\nBurnham Lake\n\nThe park features a man-made lake situated at the center where tourists can enjoy boating with rented boats.</string>

    <string name="boracay_island_title">Boracay Island</string>
    <string name="boracay_island_desc">Boracay is a small island in the Philippines located approximately 315 km (196 mi) south of Manila and 2 km off the northwest tip of Panay Island in Western Visayas region of the Philippines. Boracay Island and its beaches have received awards from numerous travel publications and agencies. The island comprises the barangays of Manoc-Manoc, Balabag, and Yapak in the municipality of Malay, in Aklan Province. The island is administered by the Philippine Tourism Authority and the provincial government of Aklan. Apart from its white sand beaches, Boracay is also famous for being one of the world\'s top destinations for relaxation. It is also emerging among the top destinations for tranquility and nightlife.\n\nIn 2012, Boracay was awarded as the best island in the world from the international travel magazine Travel + Leisure.</string>
    <string name="boracay_parasailing_title">Parasailing</string>
    <string name="boracay_parasailing_desc">Imagine being whisked into the sky while strapped in a seat covered by a colorful parachute! Parasailing had been a popular activity where riders can view the beautiful shoreline of white beach from above while being pulled by a boat. This is a fun and exciting experience for those who love heights and want a birds-eye-view of paradise.\n\nParasailing, also known as parascending or parakiting, is a recreational kiting activity where a person is towed behind a vehicle (usually a boat) while attached to a specially designed canopy wing that reminds one of a parachute, known as a parasail wing.</string>
    <string name="boracay_helmet_diving_title">Helmet Diving</string>
    <string name="boracay_helmet_diving_desc">Ever wonder what it feels like to walk on the ocean floor? Helmet Diving allows you to climb down a ladder until you reach a sea bed (around 10 ft. below the surface) while wearing a helmet made of glass plates. The helmet makes it possible for you to breathe underwater while marveling at Boracay\'s colorful sea floor with an abundance of tropical fish!\n\nTry walking on the ocean floor and feed the fish under the sea with helmet diving. An awesome and a whole new experience to explore the beauty of the hidden world under.</string>

    <string name="cebu_island_title">Cebu Island</string>
    <string name="cebu_island_desc">Cebu is a first income class island province of the Philippines located in the Central Visayas region, and consisting of the main island itself and 167 surrounding islands and islets. Its capital is Cebu City, the oldest city and first capital of the Philippines, which forms part of the Cebu Metropolitan Area together with four neighboring cities (Danao City, Lapu-Lapu City, Mandaue City and Talisay City) and eight other local government units. Mactan-Cebu International Airport, located in Mactan Island, is the second busiest airport in the Philippines.</string>
    <string name="cebu_magellans_cross_title">Magellan\'s Cross</string>
    <string name="cebu_magellans_cross_desc">Magellan\'s Cross is a Christian cross planted by Portuguese and Spanish explorers as ordered by Ferdinand Magellan upon arriving in Cebu in the Philippines on  March 15 , 1521.\n\nThis cross is housed in a chapel next to the Basilica Minore del Santo Niño on Magallanes Street (Magalhaes is the Portuguese name of Magellan), just in front of the city center of Cebu City. A sign below the cross describes the original cross is encased inside the wooden cross that is found in the center of the chapel. This is to protect the original cross from people who chipped away parts of the cross for souvenir purposes or in the belief that the cross possesses miraculous powers.</string>
    <string name="cebu_sinulog_title">Sinulog Festival</string>
    <string name="cebu_sinulog_desc">The Sinulog-Santo Niño Festival is an annual cultural and religious festival held on the third Sunday of January in Cebu City, and is the center of the Santo Niño Catholic celebrations in the Philippines.\n\nOne of the main highlights of the festival is the grand street parade which lasts for 9 to 12 hours (practically the entire day) with participants coming from the different towns and cities of Cebu and from Luzon, Visayas and Mindanao across the Philippines. The Sinulog dance contingents are dressed in bright coloured costumes dancing gracefully to the rhythm of drums, trumpet and native gongs. </string>

    <string name="palawan_underground_river_title">Underground River</string>
    <string name="palawan_underground_river_desc">The Puerto Princesa Subterranean River National Park is a protected area of the Philippines located about 80 kilometres (50 mi) north of the city centre of Puerto Princesa, Palawan. The river is also called Puerto Princesa Underground River. The national park is located in the Saint Paul Mountain Range on the western coast of the island. It is bordered by St. Paul Bay to the north and the Babuyan River to the east. The City Government of Puerto Princesa has managed the National Park since 1992. The entrance to the subterranean river is a short hike or boat ride from the town Sabang.</string>
    <string name="palawan_honda_bay_title">Honda Bay</string>
    <string name="palawan_honda_bay_desc">Just 45 minutes north of the city proper, hop onto a boat and go island hopping at Honda Bay located in the mid-eastern coast of the city. With visits to stunning islands, with white sand beaches.\n\nEach island at Honda Bay offers different thrills but Luli Island, Starfish Island, Panden Island and Cowrie Island are all great for swimming and snorkeling.</string>
    <string name="palawan_elnido_title">El Nido</string>
    <string name="palawan_elnido_desc">El Nido (officially the Municipality of El Nido) is a first class municipality and managed resource protected area in the province of Palawan in the Philippines. It is about 420 kilometres (260 mi) south-west of Manila, and about 238 kilometres (148 mi) north-east of Puerto Princesa, Palawan’s capital. It is known for its white-sand beaches, coral reefs, limestone cliffs and as the gateway to the Bacuit archipelago.\n\nEl Nido is currently ranked #1 in Condé Nast Traveler\'s list of "20 Most Beautiful Beaches in the World." CNNGo has called it the Best Beach and Island destination in the Philippines for its "extraordinary natural splendor and ecosystem."</string>
</resources>
